File manipulating?

Modes? Silencer, firemode, entire hook framework for 

outline swep structure, design for primary & secondary,

use SWEP.ClassName to register swep weapon names

Break away from stock reload function dependance, integrate clip ino stuff

Make clip gibs (client side?)

Animation play rates and seeking

Primary attack to interupt reload? @var

aim assist tick runs off of new var, not secondary.delay

Chambering pump before reload?
Make chambering optional? @ VAR

send owner primary attack anim during pump? For iron on spas, send only attak anim after attack?

Enforce Idle Functionality test

Double tap?

Make more convars to control swep features?
♦ Chambering toggle
♦ Crouch walk + Run arms think param (for gamemodes)
♦ 
♦
♦